=Just Fiancée= =Episode 10=
= مخطوبون للتو = = الحلقة 10 =
Chairman!
رئيس!
It's time to go to the company.
حان الوقت للذهاب إلى الشركة.
You're already awake, right?
أنت بالفعل مستيقظ ، أليس كذلك؟
Why do you keep looking at me?
لماذا تستمر في النظر إلي؟
I was thinking about
كنت أفكر حول
how to make it up to you.
كيف اصنعها لك.
How about
ماذا عن
going to the company with me?
الذهاب الى الشركة معي؟
You're free today, right?
أنت متفرغ اليوم ، أليس كذلك؟
Okay.
تمام.
(Max Group)
(ماكس جروب)
I can't sit here
لا أستطيع الجلوس هنا
and do nothing all day, right?
ولا تفعل شيئًا طوال اليوم ، أليس كذلك؟
Maybe I
ربما أنا
need to find a small job?
بحاجة الى العثور على عمل صغير؟
This is your job.
هذا هو عملك.
Then what can I help you with anything?
ثم ماذا يمكنني أن أساعدك في أي شيء؟
I'm going to another office.
انا ذاهب الى مكتب آخر.
Stay here.
ابق هنا.
Don't go anywhere.
لا تذهب إلى أي مكان.
I'm so bored.
اشعر بلملل.
Be a good girl.
كوني فتاة طيبة.
Luo Da,
لو دا ،
how's the Xiaolin Bay project coming along?
كيف هو مشروع خليج Xiaolin على طول؟
Chairman,
رئيس،
that project...
هذا المشروع ...
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Do you still want to let it continue?
هل ما زلت تريد السماح لها بالاستمرار؟
Since Grandpa's health is improving,
بما أن صحة الجد تتحسن ،
we surely will continue with the project.
بالتأكيد سوف نستمر في المشروع.
But
ولكن
aren't you worried that
ألست قلقًا من ذلك
it may be a trap left
قد يكون ترك فخ
by the real Miss Gu?
من قبل الآنسة جو الحقيقية؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
At that time,
فى ذلك التوقيت،
she stole important data from the company.
سرقت بيانات مهمة من الشركة.
(One year ago, in Su Yu's office)
(قبل عام واحد ، في مكتب Su Yu)
So far,
حتى الآن،
we still haven't found her.
ما زلنا لم نعثر عليها.
And yet you want to
ومع ذلك تريد
continue the project she developed.
أكمل المشروع الذي طورته.
I feel that something might go wrong.
أشعر أن شيئًا ما قد يحدث خطأ.
I don't know if I should say this.
لا أعرف ما إذا كان ينبغي أن أقول هذا.
Luo Da,
لو دا ،
you have a lot to say today.
لديك الكثير لتقوله اليوم.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
How could it be so coincidental
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك من قبيل الصدفة
that two unrelated people look so alike?
أن شخصين غير مرتبطين يتشابهان إلى هذا الحد؟
Chairman,
رئيس،
I think you should be careful.
أعتقد أنك يجب أن تكون حذرا.
I need to get something.
أنا بحاجة للحصول على شيء.
Don't forget the meeting later.
لا تنس الاجتماع لاحقًا.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
How could it be so coincidental...
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك من قبيل الصدفة ...
I think you should be careful.
أعتقد أنك يجب أن تكون حذرا.
Show me your hand.
أرني يدك.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I dropped your pen.
لقد تركت قلمك.
That's alright.
لا بأس.
What is with you?
ماذا بك
You're acting so weird.
أنت تتصرف بغرابة.
Luo Da told me we have a meeting.
أخبرني لوه دا أن لدينا اجتماع.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
The Xiaolin Bay project
مشروع خليج Xiaolin
was proposed by Gu Manman.
تم اقتراحه من قبل Gu Manman.
Attend the meeting with me.
احضر الاجتماع معي.
(Max Group, Discussion on Xiaolin Bay Project) I called everyone to this meeting
(مجموعة ماكس ، مناقشة حول مشروع خليج شياولين) دعوت الجميع إلى هذا الاجتماع
to make an announcement.
للإعلان.
(Zhong Qiuyan, Max Group Shareholder)
(Zhong Qiuyan ، مساهم Max Group)
(Zhou Wenshan, Max Group Shareholder) The Xiaolin Bay Project,
(Zhou Wenshan ، مساهم في Max Group) مشروع خليج Xiaolin ،
we are not continuing the project.
نحن لا نواصل المشروع.
Chairman,
رئيس،
are you sure you want to cancel
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد إلغاء
the tourism project at Xiaolin Bay?
مشروع السياحة في خليج Xiaolin؟
The villagers there are waiting for us to...
القرويون هناك ينتظرون منا ...
To do what?
لفعل ماذا؟
You...
أنت...
Chairman,
رئيس،
didn't we come to an agreement
ألم نتوصل إلى اتفاق
to develop a tourism project there?
لتطوير مشروع سياحي هناك؟
It is intended to stimulate the economy there
الغرض منه هو تحفيز الاقتصاد هناك
and improve the lives of the villagers.
وتحسين حياة القرويين.
We are businessmen,
نحن رجال أعمال ،
not philanthropists.
ليس فاعلي الخير.
The project will take too much time.
سيستغرق المشروع الكثير من الوقت.
It's not favorable
إنها ليست مواتية
for the company's development.
لتطوير الشركة.
Miss Gu was the one leading the project.
كانت الآنسة جو هي التي قادت المشروع.
Do you agree with what he said?
هل توافق على ما قاله؟
Does Miss Gu's opinion matter?
هل رأي الآنسة قو مهم؟
I have decided to cancel the project!
لقد قررت إلغاء المشروع!
Those in favor, raise your hand.
أولئك الذين يؤيدون ، ارفعوا أيديكم.
Raise your hand.
ارفع يدك.